[
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            1
        ],
        "question": "What is the main goal of this notebook?",
         "answer": "To build a product recommendation system for e-commerce businesses.",
         "task": "Recommendation Systems",
         "skill": "Deep Neural Networks"
    },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            1
        ],
        "question": "What are the three parts of the recommendation system this notebook is designed around?",
        "answer": "1. Product popularity based system for new customers, 2. Model-based collaborative filtering based on purchase history and ratings, 3. System for new websites without existing ratings",
         "task": "Recommendation Systems",
         "skill": "Deep Neural Networks"
    },
      {
         "cell_ids": [
            1
        ],
        "question": "What type of collaborative filtering is used in model II?",
         "answer": "Model-based collaborative filtering.",
         "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Collaborative Filtering"
    },
  {
        "cell_ids": [
            1
        ],
          "question": "What is the recommendation system in Part I targeted at?",
        "answer": "It is targeted at new customers, recommending the most popular products sold by a business.",
         "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Deep Neural Networks"
    },
   {
         "cell_ids": [
           3
        ],
          "question": "Which metric is used in collaborative filtering models in this notebook?",
         "answer": "Cosine Similarity",
          "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Collaborative Filtering"
     },
    {
        "cell_ids": [
            5
        ],
        "question": "What does the `pivot_table` method do?",
        "answer": "It creates a pivot table from the data, based on UserID, StockCode and Quantity.",
        "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
  {
        "cell_ids": [
            6
        ],
        "question": "What is used as input to the filtering?",
         "answer": "The reviews of products are used to produce recommendation based on the similarity of reviews",
          "task":"Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Deep Neural Networks"
    },
     {
         "cell_ids": [
            13
         ],
        "question":"What does the variable X represents in part 3?",
        "answer": "It represents the transpose of the utility matrix that we got from our pivot table.",
          "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
        "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
      },
 {
        "cell_ids": [
            13
        ],
       "question": "What is the use of singular value decomposition (SVD) algorithm in this notebook?",
         "answer":"To decompose the user-item rating matrix into two smaller matrices.",
         "task": "Principal Component Analysis",
        "skill": "Kernel PCA"
   },
   {
      "cell_ids": [
            16
        ],
        "question": "what does the code `recommend` method returns?",
          "answer":"It returns a list of top 30 similar restaurants, then filters out duplicate values and returns top 10 results based on mean ratings.",
          "task": "Recommendation Systems",
        "skill": "Deep Neural Networks"
    }
]